- 好了吗小比 - 好了小泰
- Ready, b? - Ready, t.
好
Okay.
故事说的是我们的两个超级老爸
This is the story of our most excellent dads.
我是比尔S普雷斯顿 时尚先生
I'm bill s. Preston, esquire.
我是泰德·罗根 人称希雅多
And I'm Ted "Theodore" Logan.
我们是威史组合
And we're wyld stallyns!
这也许是你们初见他们
This was probably the first time you saw 'em.
突发新闻 威史组合吸引众多观众
就在我们出生前不久
Not long before we were born,
有人让他们写首歌
they were told they were gonna write a song
这首歌能团结全世界
that was gonna unite the entire world.
也就是他们认为的主打歌
Which they thought they had done with their hit single,
"摇滚者"
"those who rock."
结果非但没能团结全世界
Not only did it not unite the world...
他们的乐队反倒崩溃了
But the band fell apart.
老爸们现在已分开 但他们仍在努力
And our dads, alone now, were trying harder and harder.
但问题是 老爸们越努力
But the problem was, the harder dads tried...
别人对他们的音乐就越不感兴趣
The less interested people seemed to be in their music.
受影响的不只是他们和家人
Not only was it wearing on them and on the family.
就连他们本该团结的全世界
But the universe they were told they were gonna bring together,
都开始崩溃
was actually starting to unravel.
连时间都崩溃了
Yeah, time was folding in on itself.
太糟糕了
It was bad.
怎么了
What?
没开玩笑
Totally, dude.
噪起来
Make some noise!
所以才有这部续集
Anyways, this is how we got to where we are now.
大家好亲朋好友们
Hello, friends and loved ones.
欢迎各位齐聚一堂
To this most joyous of occasions!
泰德和我认识蜜西几十年
Ted and I have known missy in different capacities
每次她的身份不同
for many decades.
首先 她是我们十岁时的保姆
First, she was our babysitter when we were ten.
然后 我们都邀请她参加舞会
Then we both invited her to the prom when she was a senior and we were freshmen.
而蜜西则成了我妈
and missy became mom.
她跟比尔的爸爸离婚后 却嫁给了我爸
After divorcing bill's dad, she married my dad
- 成为我妈 - 是啊
- and became my mom. - Yeah.
现在她要嫁给泰德的弟弟
And now she's marrying Ted's little brother,
即迪肯·罗根警官
officer Deacon Logan.
迪肯与蜜西 新婚快乐
蜜西 比尔和我
Missy, bill and I,
还有我漂亮的老婆伊丽莎白
along with my beautiful wife, Elizabeth,
我们的女儿比莉
and our daughter, Billie.
我的漂亮老婆乔安娜 我们的女儿希雅
And my beautiful wife, Joanna, and our daughter, thea,
都欢迎你的回归
all wanna welcome you back.
张开双臂
With open arms.
不仅如此
This happy event would seem to make
迪肯成了自己的父亲
Deacon his own father-in-law
泰德成了自己的叔叔
and Ted his own uncle.
更不用说 我爸成了自己的儿子
Not to mention making my dad his own son.
借着这美好的想法
And with that beautiful thought in mind,
第一支舞的伴奏
for your first dance,
将献上我们的作品
we wish to present you with a matrimonial offering.
作为全球首演 泄露给你们
A sneak peek at the world premiere of our newest Sonic creation.
不确定这首歌能否团结世界
We're not sure if this is going to be the song that unites the world.
但我们觉得
We're pretty sure it might.
- 应该会 - 是啊
- At least we hope. - Yeah.
肯定是又一首威史组合的打榜单曲
Sure to be another real doozy from the wyld stallyns.
测试 一二三
Check one two three.
跳舞吧 小迪基
Let's dance, freaky deaky.
好的 亲亲蜜西
You got it, kissy missy.
你爸过去常这样叫我
Your dad used to call me that.
知道
Totally aware of that, babe.
请欣赏前三曲
Please enjoy the first three movements of...
"联系我们的时间"
"That which binds us through time."
"化学物理和生物之爱"
The chemical, physical, and biological nature of love.
"探索意义的意义"
An exploration of the meaning of meaning.
第一部
Part one. Ah.
- 准备 比尔 - 好了 泰德
- Ready, bill? - Ready, Ted.
一 -  二
- One. - Two.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
爸爸 我跟你讲了无数次
Dad, I've told you a thousand times,
比尔和我会一直创作
bill and I have to keep going till...
对 直到你们的音乐团结世界
Yeah. Till your music unites the world.
罗根警长 未来的人告诉我们
Chief Logan, the people in the future told us...
- 比尔 你没有时间旅行 - 我们有
- Bill, you didn't time-travel. - We did.
你们的老婆们 并非来自中世纪的英国
Your wives aren't from medieval england.
她们是啊
They are.
- 你们也没去过天堂地狱 - 我们去了
- And you didn't go to heaven and hell. - We did!
- 你们没有 - 我们去了
- You didn't! - We did!
知道为什么吗
And you know why?
因为这不可能
Because it's impossible.
给你们俩出个好主意
Here's a real idea for you two.
又来了
Here it comes, dude.
找份正经工作
Get real jobs.
为你们女儿做榜样
Be role models to your daughters.
算了
Oh, never mind.
你们啊
You are.
她们24岁了 非但住在家里
They're 24, they live at home
还失业
and they're unemployed.
还记得以前叫她们"小比尔小泰德"吗
You remember when you used to call them "little bill," "little Ted"?
挺好听的 爷爷
We thought it was cute, gramps. Hey.
简直像被下了咒
Yeah. Well, it turned out to be a curse.
她们整天闲逛 听音乐
All I ever see them do is sit around, listen to music.
我们就是这样 绝对的
That is our primary activity, definitely. Yeah.
没事吧
You guys okay?
乔安娜 伊丽莎白
Joanna, Elizabeth,
作为家里唯一有工作的成年人
how do you feel about being the only adults in your families?
你们是什么想法
The only ones with actual jobs?
收拾东西
Let's pack up.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
很谢谢你
I really appreciate you doing this.
虽然你没得选
I know it wasn't your choice.
不客气 乔
Of course, Jo.
希望对我们有用
I really want this to work for both of us.
好的
Yeanh.
你好
Oh, hey.
最近好吗
How's it goin', dude?
很好
Great, dude.
- 晦 - 乔
- Hi! - Hey, Jo.
不
Oh, no, no.
是今天吗
I'm sorry, is this the right day?
就是今天
Yeah, totally.
你们的老婆感觉超怪异
So, do you understand why this situation
你们明白吗
might seem at all strange to your wives?
完全不明白 何来此说
No. Not at all. Why?
老婆们建议夫妻治疗
Well, when your wives suggested couples therapy,
你认为这是她们的想法吗
do you think that this is what they had in mind?
绝对是
Well, definitely.
我们是一对又一对
I mean, we're a couple of couples, right?
说的没错
- That is true. - Yeah.
但通常情况下 夫妻治疗
But usually, with couples therapy,
指的是一对夫妇
it just means one couple.
- 真的呀 - 是啊
- That makes sense. - Yeah.
但既然你们都来了
Well, but, you know, we're here,
那就开始治疗吧
so let's work with that.
- 可以吗 - 好的
Yes? Yeah.
好的
Okay, great.
泰德 你有话说给老婆听吗
Ted, is there something you feel your wife needs to hear from you?
有啊
Yeah. Totally.
我们爱你们
We love you guys.
这句很好
Oh, that is good, dude.
在某种程度上
In a way, yes.
被爱当然是很好的
I mean, it is great to feel loved.
但你们知道吗
But do you understand
也许你们老婆听了会很怪
how that might sound strange to your wives?
我说的是比尔
I'll shoot this at bill.
不
No.
我是说 我们爱她们
I mean, we love 'em.
"我们爱她们"
"We love them."
- 是啊 - 我们爱她们
Yeanh. Yeah. We do.
关键词是"我们"
Okay. It's the "we" part.
泰德你能重复吗
Ted, can you say the same thing,
但不要说我们 而是说我
but instead of "we," say "I" in the sentence.
- 对 - 好的
- Oh. Yeah. - Okay.
当然
Of course.
好
Okay.
- 伊丽莎白 - 在
- Elizabeth? - Yes.
我和比尔 爱你和乔安娜
I and bill love you and Joanna.
好
Okay.
别怪我多嘴
Dude, with all due respect,
我觉得你不明白
I don't think you're quite getting this.
- 那你来吧 - 好的
- Okay go for it, dude. - Okay.
我来说
I'm gonna do one.
说吧
Yes, go for it, dude.
- 好 - 好
- Great. - Okay.
乔安娜
Joanna?
发自我的肺腑之言
From the very, very bottom of I
也包括泰德
and Ted's hearts,
我和泰德 喜欢并且爱着你和伊丽莎白
I and Ted, totally love and worship you and Elizabeth.
- 说的真好 - 真棒谢谢
- Perfect, dude. - Awesome, dude, thanks.
乔安娜 你或伊丽莎白想回应一下吗
Joanna, would you or Elizabeth like to respond to that?
那么你
Oh. Well, would you...
我们两个有点难
Well, it has been tough for us.
家里
At home.
连续25年
You know, it's been so hard watching you
看着你们两个头撞南墙也不回
beat your heads against the wall for 25 years
我不知道我们还能坚持多久
and I'm not sure how much longer we can keep going on like this.
什么
What? Well...
比尔 泰德
Bill, Ted.
最后我想跟你们老婆说两句
I'd love to spend the last part of this session with your wives.
- 单独吗 - 对单独
- Alone? - Yes, alone.
好
Right. Okay.
那么家里见
We'll see you at home, okay?
好的
Okay. All right, then. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
原来她们是这样想的
Dude, did you know they felt that way?
这问题得解决
We have to fix this.
关键她们说得对 比尔
The thing is, they're right, bill.
她们是公主
They're princesses.
是啊
Yeanh.
我们把她们拖入了我们的世界
We pulled them out of their lives to be here with us.
她们并没想这样
And they didn't come all this way for this.
所以我们要努力
That's why we gotta keep working, dude.
这不就是问题吗
But isn't that the problem?
是问题也是解决方法
Yeah. But it's also the solution.
我猜也是
Yeah. I guess.
超凡脱俗
Dude, this is transcendent.
66年菲尔默音乐节
Is this Fillmore '667
不 蒙特利67年的音乐节
no, monterey pop, '67.
第二次试音 曲目的名字是
That second sound check where they did that riff
"奇异恩典"
on amazing grace.
老爸们好
How's it goin', dads?
女儿们好
How's it goin', girls?
治疗如何
How was therapy?
非常棒
- It went okay. - Yeah.
爸爸 还有 爷爷错了
Hey, dad, by the way, gramps was wrong.
婚礼上的伴奏太棒了
The wedding song was most luminous.
谢谢 小比
Oh, thank you, b.
很高兴你明白 比莉
Glad you dug it, Billie.
不 说真的 泰德叔叔
No, seriously, uncle Ted,
你的电子琴怎么弹的如此优秀
when did you get so excellent on theremin?
这节奏好到没天理 我没开玩笑
Your playing rivaled, and I'm not kidding,
简直可以媲美克拉拉·洛克莫
Clara rockmore.
谢谢 小泰
Thanks, t.
和她比 我太受抬举了
Clara rockmore was definitely an inspiration.
是啊
Yeanh.
比尔叔叔
- And, uncle bill! - Yeah.
用喉咙唱歌
The throat singing, I mean,
达到了全新的口才境界
it was a whole new level of eloquence.
这是一种新型的喊麦
Some serious buga khoomel.
姑娘们 你们的音乐天分令人赞赏
Your musical acumen is most impressive, girls.
- 爸爸 祝你们这首歌好运 - 能行的
- Hey dad, good luck on the song. - You got this.
怎么了 泰德
What is it, Ted?
小伊说得对
Liz is right.
我们头撞南墙25年
We have been banging our heads against a wall for 25 years.
我累了
And I'm tired, dude.
泰德
Ted.
我们还有大好前途
We have a destiny to fulfill.
对
Yeanh.
想想我们的粉丝
And think about our fans, dude.
鲍勃和温迪会理解的
Bob and Wendy will totally understand.
至于艾琳 好几年没她的音讯
Eileen we haven't heard from for several years.
比尔
Bill?
什么
What?
我昨天去了赛勒斯阿德勒音乐公司
I went into Cyrus adler music yesterday.
他说给我6400美元 买那把莱斯保罗
He said he'd give me $6,400 for the les Paul.
你是说
Are you saying...
是的
Yeanh.
我想是的
I think I am.
嘱
Yeanh.
哇
Whoa!
姐们
Dude! Dude!
这是未来
It's the future!
你好 朋友
Greetings, my excellent friends...
我们认识你吗
Do we know you?
我是凯莉
I'm Kelly.
等等 你是鲁弗斯的女儿
Wait, you're Rufus' daughter!
是我
I am.
我这辈子都想见到你们
And I've been wanting to meet you my whole life.
你一定很失望吧
It must be very disappointing.
一点也不
Not at all.
我们有麻烦了 先生们
We have a problem, gentlemen.
可能是很严重的问题
Potentially a very serious problem.
关于音乐吗
About the music?
是的他们只想谈谈
About the music. They just wanna talk to you.
我预感不妙
Dude, I got a very bad feeling about this.
没事的 泰德
It'll be fine, Ted.
未来会喜欢我们的
They totally love us in the future, dude.
哇
Whoa!
老爸们有麻烦了
Dude, our dads are totally in trouble.
对他们不公平
I feel so bad for 'em.
他们一直靠自己
They've been doing this on their own for the longest time.
我希望有办法帮他们
Yeah, I wish there was some way we could help 'em out, you know?
好的
Yeanh.
但怎么帮
But how? Whoa!
加州 圣迪马斯 2720年
- 大哥 - 什么事
Dude. Yeah?
- 未来 - 是啊
- The future. - Yeah.
鲁弗斯
Rufus.
朋友们你们好
Greetings, my excellent friends.
你们看到的初级电话亭
What you're looking at is the original phone booth...
先生们
Gentlemen?
是我第一次访问伟人时用过的
That I used on my first visit to the great ones
早在1989年
way back in 1989.
预言告诉我们
The prophecy tells us...
比尔和泰德
Bill and Ted.
上前
Step forward.
你们好啊
How's it goin'?
伟人
Great ones?
那个
It's, uh...
回来真好
It's good to be back.
我们想说什么
What have you got to say for yourselves?
要
Be
善待彼此
Excellent to each other.
尽情派对
- And party on, dudes. - Yeah.
二十五年前
Twenty-five years ago,
威史组合举办了一场音乐会
wyld stallyns played a concert
在大峡谷
at the Grand Canyon.
没错
That's true.
一个月前
One month ago,
你们演奏了"糜鹿小屋"给40个人
you played the elks lodge
地点是加州巴斯托
in barstow, California, for 40 people,
大多数人只是冲着两块钱的墨西哥卷饼去的
most of whom were there only because it was $2 taco night,
虽然我对此很不解
whatever the hell that means.
- 说的没错 - 没错
Well, yeah. We did! Yeah. We did!
你们应该用歌声团结全世界
You were supposed to unite the world in song.
她父亲说
According to her father,
一首由普雷斯顿/罗根创作的歌曲
a song created by preston/logan...
说的是我们
That's us, dude.
将由乐队全体成员表演
At a concert performed by everyone in the band
时间是17时
at 7:17 P.M.
地点是MP46
At mp 46,
说的就是今晚
that's tonight,
这将拯救我们的现实
will save reality as we know it,
并团结从古至今的全人类
uniting humanity across all time.
等等
Wait...
对不起
I'm sorry.
你说什么
What?
你是说
Did you say,
"我们的现实"
"reality as we know it"?
是的
Yes! Oh!
77分25秒后 必须听到这首歌
We need to hear the song in 77 minutes and 25 seconds.
这里有你们需要的一切
You have everything you require.
去工作吧
Get to work.
他们恨我们
Dude, they totally hate us.
我根本就没听说过MP46
And I've never even heard of mp 46.
是啊
Yeanh.
凯莉
Kelly!
一首歌如何拯救现实
How does a song save reality?
我无法告诉你 但这是必须的
That I can't tell you, but it has to.
不管怎样都得行
Somehow.
大唱盘正在倾覆
The great turntable is tipping.
那里是时间和空间的中心
That there is the center of space and time.
七百年前的圣迪马斯 晚上七点十七分
San dimas 700 years ago, 7:17 P.M.
我父亲相信这首歌
My father believed that the song
是人类进入和谐节奏的交汇点
could be the nexus point that brings humanity into rhythm and Harmony.
- 如何 - 我们最近才发现的
- How? - We only discovered this recently,
但没有它 现实就会崩溃
but without it, reality will collapse,
而时空将不复存在
and time and space will cease to exist.
下午17点
So until 7:17 P.M...
一切旨有可能
Anything is possible.
下午17点之后呢
And after 7:17 P.M.?
没有这首歌 也就没有17点之后了
Without the song, there is no after 7:17 P.M.
这是我爸爸的 他想给你们
This was my dad's. He'd want you to have it.
用来掌握圣迪马斯的时间
It'll help keep track of the time in San dimas.
"有时候 不到最后"
"Sometimes things don't make sense."
"事情就没有意义"
"Until the end of the story."
我爸的口头禅
That's what my dad always said.
那就不打扰你们了
I'll leave you to it?
好
Okay.
我们现在要写出一首巨作
Now alls we gotta do is write the greatest song ever written.
让世界和谐
That brings the entire world into rhythm and Harmony.
并拯救现实
And saves reality as we know it.
从古
All through...
至今
Time.
这首团结全世界的歌
Dude. We've spent our whole life
我们写了一辈子
trying to write the song that will unite the world.
凭什么75分钟后就能写出
What makes us think we can write it in, like, 75 minutes?
泰德 必须写
Ted, we had to have written that song.
未来世界的人让我们写
The people in the future told us we did.
话虽如此
Yeah. I guess.
这说明我们有能力
Which means we have it in us, dude.
只是时机还没到
Maybe we just haven't written it yet.
写还是要写的
Maybe we're still gonna.
既然我们还没写出来
Well, if we haven't written it yet,
那未来怎么会写出来呢
but we know we're gonna at some point,
反正我们未来都会写好 不如直接去未来
why can't we just go to the future when we have written it?
- 抄我们自己的 - 说得对
- And take it from ourselves! - Yeah!
泰德 这些年你有反人类的想法
Ted! You have had many counterintuitive ideas over the years,
这是最惊天动地的一个
but this is by far the counterintuitivest of them all, dude!
但问题是
Except,
偷自己的算偷吗
won't that be stealing?
既然是我们自己的 那怎么能算偷呢
How is that stealing if we're stealing it from ourselves, dude?
也是
Yeah. Yeah.
希望还奏效
- I hope it still works. - Yeah.
我们要去多久后的未来
How far into our future do you think we gotta go?
那得看我们什么时候写的歌
It depends on when we think we wrote that song.
保守一点吧 两年
Let's be conservative. Say, two years?
可以 泰德
Sounds good, Ted.
我们拿到歌曲之后
Then, once we get the song,
就回到原来的时间
we'll go back home to right before we left.
时间回路
然后呢
And then what?
团结世界 拯救现实
Unite the world and save reality, dude.
- 比尔 我的朋友 - 泰德 我的朋友
- Bill, my friend. - Yes, Ted, my friend?
我有一种感觉 世界即将完美改变
I have a feeling things are about to change in a most outstanding way.
百分之二百同意
I could not agree more.
加州 圣迪马斯 2022年
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You okay, dude? - Yeah.
- 你呢 - 没事儿
You? Yeah.
去跟未来的我们问好 然后拿歌
Let's go say hello to ourselves and get that song.
长久不用都生锈了
It's our rusty bucket, dude. To those who rock
这里
over here, dude.
他们说我们只是说说而已，但我们是在散步
They say we're talking the talk but we're walking the walk
等等谁在演奏"摇滚者"
wait. We're playing those who rock?
在这里
Here?
摇滚耶
Rock, yeah!
我们是摇滚者
We are those who rock
各位
everybody!
我们是摇滚者
We are those who rock
拍手
clap your hands now!
我们是摇滚者
We are those who rock
耶摇滚
yeah, rock!
是我们啊
Dude, that's us!
别看 他们就看不到我们
Don't look and they won't see us, dude!
比尔 等等
Bill, wait!
走 走 走
Go, go, go!
- 快到货车了 - 我们的 站住
- Almost at the Van! - Hey, us's, stop!
你们嗯好
Oh, hello!
我们完全忘了你们会来
We totally forgot you were coming.
见到你们真好
- Yeah. - How great to see you.
你们在说什么 你们在躲我们
What are you talking about? You totally ran away from us.
我知道你们在想什么
Look, guys, we know exactly what you're thinking.
为什么我们要在18:15演奏"麦克风之夜"呢
Why would we be playing open mic night at 6:15 P.M.
既然我们是摇滚明星
When, in fact, we have become such huge rock stars again.
是啊
Yeanh.
我的解释是
Here's the answer.
我们在这里是一种讽刺幽默
- Yeah. - Us being here is humorously ironic.
你相信我们吗
Do you believe us?
- 不 - 完全不信
- No. - Not at all.
很遗憾你这么想
Well, I feel sorry for you, then.
我们来早了 这时候我们还没写出那首歌
Dude, I think we came too early. These other us's don't have the song.
自己写啊 别偷我们的
Why don't you go write it yourselves instead of trying to steal it from us?
是你不会写 泰德
You're the one who couldn't write it, Ted.
你老婆跑了 泰德
Well, you're the one who lost his wife, Ted.
什么
What?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
事情是这样的 比尔
Oh! Here's what happened, bill.
在夫妻治疗失败后
After you failed couples therapy,
小伊和小乔被未来人拜访
Liz and Jo were visited by other thems from the future
寻找另一种生活
looking for just one life
一种幸福的生活
where they could be happy with you!
猜怎么着
And guess what?
她们没找到
They didn't find one!
我们俩只好单身两年
And now we've been alone for two years
因为你们害我们没老婆
'cause you sent our wives away.
不可能
No way.
有可能
Yes way!
我们的老婆离开两年
Our wives have been gone for two years
而你们却什么都没做
and you didn't do anything about it?
都是你们害的
You did, all right.
你们回去后 把事搅黄了
You went back and you made it worse.
还有呢
And guess what else?
女儿们也不愿意和你们说话
Your daughters won't even talk to you.
什么
What?
你们是混蛋 泰德
You're a dick, Ted.
- 要不要吃屎 泰德 - 泰德 不值得
- You want a piece of me, Ted? - Ted, he's not worth it!
不值得 我们得走了
Hey! It's not worth it, dude. We gotta go.
并拯救我们的婚姻
Yeah! And save our marriages.
废柴 过气的人
Losers! Has-beens!
- 搞什么鬼 - 别跟自己打架
- Whatever! - Stop fighting with yourself!
昙花一现们
Flashes in the pans!
别跟自己打架
Stop fighting with yourself!
不顺
That did not go well.
是啊你们很好斗
Yeah. And your you is a very contentious dickweed.
比尔我们得回去和小伊和小乔谈谈
Bill, we gotta go back and talk with Liz and Jo.
好的
On it, dude.
求你了妈妈爸爸说普雷斯顿/罗根
所有乐团成员都会团结
And everyone in the band will unite...
我记得他说的每一个字
I remember what he said. Every word.
给他们一个机会
Well, then, give them a chance.
我什么都给了
I gave them a chance and everything they could possibly need,
但他们还是逃走了
but they bolted.
凯莉
Kelly,
你父亲和我从来没有分歧
you know your father and I agreed on everything,
但根据他得到的信息 可能有别的原因
but there are other interpretations of the information he was acting on.
我知道
I'm aware of that.
委员会很多人认为
Many on the council believe that it is, in fact,
比尔和泰德的死 将带来新时代
the death of bill and Ted that will bring the new epoch.
我不同意
Well, I disagree with that completely!
过分
That's atrocious!
等以后你成了大领袖
Well, maybe someday when you're the great leader,
你可以做出影响时空的决定
you can make the decisions that will affect all time and space.
你不能只说领袖吗
You could just say "leader."
- 太自命不凡了 - 准备
- So pretentious. - Is it ready?
好了 大领袖 应该好了
Yes, great leader. It should be.
- 什么叫应该 - 已经好了
- "Should be"? - Is.
女士
Madam.
知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
知道 大领袖
Yes, great leader.
怎么做
You know what to do.
你不能失败
You must not fail.
不
Must
能
not
失败
fail.
你竟然想杀比尔和泰德
I cannot believe you're gonna kill bill and Ted!
爸爸会被你气死的
Dad would be so mad at you.
我们没有选择 凯尔
We're out of options, kel.
序幕开始了
The unravelling has already begun.
未来人 你回来了
Future dude! You're back?
我在找你们父亲 他们在吗
I'm looking for your fathers. Have they been here?
不在
No.
爸爸们在哪里
Where are our dads?
他们在遭受磨难
They're in a tribulation, aren't they?
是的
They are.
不要透露你们看到了可怕的未来机器人
Listen, you didn't see a scary-looking robot
我妈总是很过分 刚派了一个机器人
去找我们的爸爸
- Just sent one. - To get our dads?
别担心 不可能
Don't worry. I won't let that happen.
我们也想帮他们
Well, we're trying to help 'em, too.
嘿
Hey.
这玩意可以
Hey, this can go, like...
可以
Like...
进行时间旅行对吗
Like, anywhere, right? Like, all throughout time?
说得对 但我现在要留下
That's correct, but I need to stay.
我妈的使者会到这里来找他们
My guess is that my mom's emissary will be looking for them here.
好
Well,
希雅和我
thea and I were gonna help our dads with their music
打算帮爸爸们做音乐 小样
by putting together samples for 'em.
我们能组成真正的乐队
Yeah, but now it appears we could put together an actual band.
就他们的话 也太孤单
I mean, it's just them, and they're all alone!
在等可怕的机器人的同时
Hey, so, do you mind while you stay here and wait for the scary-looking robot,
请你演示时空机的用法吧
you could show us how to use the booth?
得记住
Dude, we gotta remember.
做好不做坏
Make it better, not worse!
嗯 希望她们还在
Yeah. I hope they're still there.
他们身上的工作
It's just that the job that they've been given, it is...
- 不可能 - 不可能
- Impossible. - Impossible.
- 乔安娜 - 伊丽莎白
- Joanna! - Elizabeth!
跟你们聊聊
- Hi! - We need to talk to you.
"我们"回来了
And we're back.
事情很重要伍德医生
This is super important, Dr. wood.
我们看到了两年后的自己
We just saw ourselves two years in the future.
你们又穿越时空了
Wait, you're time-travelling again?
这次是去救现实
Only to save reality as we know it.
好 也许
Okay. Maybe...
但事情更糟了
But we just found out something way worse.
- 你们会离开我们 - 什么
You're leaving us. “What?
- 我们不会 - 我们有吗
- What? No, we're not. - No, are we?
是的
Yes. You are.
而且你们有很好的理由 小乔
Yeah. And you have real good reason to, Jo.
因为我们未来住在拖车里
'Cause we seriously appear to be living in our Van.
就是那辆拖车
Dude, we are totally living in that Van.
而且我还酗酒
And I'm drinking way too much.
- 你根本不喝酒的 - 还没喝
- Darling, you don't even drink. - Not yet.
但我肯定会酗了
But I'm going to. A lot.
- 什么 - 还有那个谎言
- What? - Yeah. And the lying.
你们不会相信我们成了骗子
You cannot believe what liars we are.
说谎的废柴
Yeah, desperate, pathetic, lying losers.
不 不 我的天
Oh, no! Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
好 停一停 都别急
Okay, let's stop for a moment and take notice of the dynamic.
你们担心失去
Threatened by the thought of losing your...
- 公主们 - 就是这个词
Princesses. Sure. That's a word.
我们确实是公主
No, we actually are princesses.
我们出生在1410年 是1408年
We were bornin 1410. 1408.
我们为什么离开你们
Okay. What about us leaving you?
天啊
Oh, man.
所以我们回来
That's totally why we're here.
为了证明我们不是未来的那两个废柴
Yeah. To prove that we're not the losers we just saw we were.
就算那些废柴警告我们别和你们说话
Even though those loser us's tried to tell us not to come and talk to you.
感觉会把事情弄糟一样
Yeah. Like we were somehow gonna make it worse.
但我们没把事情弄糟 对吧
But we're not making it worse, right?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth?
乔安娜
Joanna?
伍德医生
Dr. wood?
看来弄糟了
Dude, we totally made it worse.
- 等下回来 - 我们会纠正
We'll be back. And make it better.
你说的1408年是指
When you say 1408, you mean the year...
最后一件事
- One last thing. - Yeah.
未来的你们马上要出现
Older yous from the future are just about to show up
带你们去寻找幸福生活
to take you on a trip in search of a happy life with us.
不要去 因为你们找不到幸福
Don't go. 'Cause you're not gonna find one.
是 但你们会去
Yeah, but you're gonna go.
- 要去 - 不去吗
- So, don't go. - So, go?
还是去吧
No. I guess, go.
我们爱你们
We love you guys.
会搞定的
We're gonna fix it.
糟透了
That went terrible, dude.
未来两年显然不够
Two years forward was clearly not enough.
这次试试五年吧
Let's try five this time.
我开始想念小伊了
Dude, I miss Liz already.
坚持住泰德
Hang in there, Ted.
会好的
Things are about to get a whole lot better.
什么时间
What time is it, dude?
还剩58分钟
Fifty-eight minutes.
好了 走
Okay, let's go.
看来我们也得走
Actually, we have to go, too.
他们说未来的我们来了
Right. Those older us's they referred to are outside.
对于时间旅行我有点紧张
I'm a little bit nervous to time-travel again, to be honest.
我也是毕竟20多年没穿越了
As am I. We haven't time-traveled in more than two decades.
- 我知道 - 我说女士们
- No, I know. - You know what, ladies?
我建议每隔两三天你们来一次
I'd like to recommend we see each other a minimum of two to three,
一周五次
five days a week.
- 好 再见 - 谢谢
- All right, then. - Lovely. Thank you.
不
No. No.
第一
Nol
伦敦 1967年
成功了
It worked.
当然啊
Most indubitably.
确定是这里吗
You sure this is it?
打扰 吉米·亨德里克斯先生
Excuse me, Mr. Jimi Hendrix?
亲眼见到您是我的荣幸
Can I just say it is an honor to be in your presence, dude?
电子女儿国
Electric ladyland.
我们还能说什么呢
What can we even say?
你们两个是谁
Who are you two?
希雅·普雷斯顿也称希雅多拉
我们来帮父亲团结全世界
Yeah, we're here for our dads, to help them unite the world.
是真正的团结全世界
Like, no exaggeration, literally unite the world.
方法是组建王牌乐队
By putting together a killer band for 'em,
从你开始
and we had to start with you, dude.
所以 问题是
So, question...
你是否想成为这首伟大歌曲的关键部分
How would you like to be a key part of this epochal song?
我不想
No.
必须搞定吉米·亨德里克斯
Dude, we have to have Jimi Hendrix.
对
Yeanh.
但这个乐队默默无闻
But how are we gonna get him to be in a band
如何让他加入
with people he hasn't even heard of?
有办法
Well, okay.
那他听说过谁呢
Who's somebody he has heard of?
新奥尔良 1922年
♪ Oh, when the saints
♪ go marching in
♪ oh, when the saints go marching in
♪ well, I want to be in that number
好
all right, all right, all right. All right.
有事吗 小姐们
Can I help you, young ladies?
抱歉
Uh... we're so sorry.
请原谅我们 阿姆斯特朗先生
Please excuse us, Mr. Armstrong, sir.
想和您谈谈
Might we have a word with you?
这是奇异恩典 由吉米·亨德里克斯先生演奏
So, that is amazing grace played by a Mr. Jimi Hendrix.
他是乐队成员
Who's in the band.
特别指定要你
And specifically requested your presence, so...
所以我们才来这里
And here's why.
您的即兴创作
Your improvisations, obviously influenced
明显受到邦克·约翰逊和金奥利弗的影响
by bunk Johnson and king Oliver...
但最终还是
Yeah, but ultimately sui generis.
自成一格 先生
Totally inspired him, sir.
大家来看
You gotta come see this, fellas.
什么情况
What you got there, Lou?
你解放了所有的音乐
You liberated all music, dude.
那是什么
Hey, what's that doohickey?
加州 圣迪马斯 2025年
该死的 我们成功了
Damn it.
加州 圣迪马斯 2025年
成功了
We did it!
看我们住的地方
Dude, look at where we live!
一首歌就能搞定这一切
One song did all this?
泰德 如果不只是一首歌呢
Ted, what if it wasn't just one song?
在我们写歌拯救宇宙之后
What if after we wrote it and saved the universe,
或许又写了很多歌
a dam broke and the songs just kept comin' and comin'?
是的
Oh, yeah.
大家好
Hello!
年轻的我们 你们好
Younger us's, hello!
- 你们好 - 你们好
- Hello! - Hello!
这次 我们在等你们
This time, we were expecting you.
不像三年前那些露天麦克风的家伙
Yes, and unlike those sad open mic blokes from three years ago...
我们最终同情他们
We are now finally able to muster some compassion for them.
我们其实
We actually do have...
有料
The goods.
进你们的未来
To your futures.
- 进你们的未来 - 耶
We did it, dude. Yeah!
干杯
Cheers!
你们怎么都有英国口音
So, uh, why do you both have english accents?
有趣的故事 请坐
Funny story. Please.
比尔和我被封为骑士
Once bill and I were knighted,
小伊和小乔的事情就好办了
things got so good with Liz and Jo that we decided, as families,
去中世纪的英国避暑
to start summering in medieval england.
往事已成风
And I suppose it just bloody well rubbed off!
我们很开心
And I can't say how chuffed we are about it.
松了一口气
That is such a relief!
我得说
I must say,
我虽然不喜欢旧的我们
as much as I disliked those previous us's,
我喜欢现在的我们
I like these us's.
我对旧我没有意见
Yeah. I didn't have a big problem with that other me,
但我更喜欢新我
but I do like this other me even more.
是啊
Yeanh.
说够了 大家
Enough talking, mates.
你们全都
Are you ready...
准备好了吗
For everything...
准备改变
To change?
这真是
That is truly...
最惊人的歌曲
The most amazing song...
我听过的最棒的歌
I have ever heard.
很棒
It's great.
真没想到我们有这种能力
Honestly, I wouldn't have thought we had it in us.
但你们就是有
But you do!
现在是时候
And now it's time...
分享给全世界了
To get it out to the world.
我不会忘记你 比尔爵士
I'll never forget you, sir bill.
我也一样 比莉男孩
Right back at you, Billie boyo.
再见
So long, I guess.
谢谢
And thanks!
嗯
Yeanh.
再见了
So long.
退下
Tallyho!
奇妙
Marvelous!
泰德 你对自己为什么那么怪
Ted, why were you acting so weird with yourself, dude?
我不知道 我总这样
I don't know. I always seem to act weird with myself.
你得解决这个问题
Yeah, you do! You gotta get over that, dude.
拿到歌曲了
We got the song!
戴夫格罗尔
Dave grohl!
你们是谁
Who are you guys?
你们在我家干什么
What're you doin' in my house?
不
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
现在 就等那两个人回去改变一切
Now we'll wait for those other us's to go back and change everything.
敬我们的未来美好生活
To our lives getting a whole lot better.
嗯
Yeanh.
泰德 说真的 伏特加喝慢点
Ted, seriously, slow down on the vodka, dude.
你们完全骗了我们
You guys totally lied to us!
你们为什么不把这首歌带回圣迪马斯
Why haven't you taken the song back to San dimas?
也许是因为这不是我们的歌
Maybe 'cause it's not our song!
扯淡
Poppycock!
这是戴夫格罗尔的
It's Dave grohl's!
他在外面报警了
And he's outside right now calling the cops.
泰德 我就说戴夫格罗尔这周回来
Ted, I told you Dave grohl came back this week.
我还以为他下周回来
Totally thought he came back next week.
你们到底在想什么
What were you guys even thinking?
就因为你们俩想不出一首好歌
Just 'cause you two couldn't come up with a great song...
而戴夫格罗尔能
And Dave grohl did!
我们不该为此受到惩罚
Doesn't mean we should be punished for that.
这可不行
We're not gonna do it.
你们必须
You have to!
这是唯一追回老婆们的办法
It's your only chance to get our wives back.
这件事你们也撒谎了
You were lying about that?
我们当然撒谎了
Of course we were lying.
天啊
Oh, man.
她们不想和你们扯上关系
Yeah, they don't want anything to do with youl!
因为她们穿越时空
'Cause they traveled all through time
最后意识到你们是废柴
and finally realized you are losers.
是啊因为你们做了错误的选择
Yeah, 'cause you make bad choices.
就像这样
Like this.
现在 把这首歌
Now, take the song!
大家 说真的
Guys, seriously,
不必拿枪指着我们
you don't have to pull guns on us.
是吗 不然怎样
Yeah? Watch what happens when we don't.
看到吗
See?
我不得不承认 比尔 你说得对
I have to admit, bill. You were right.
泰德
Ted!
- 你们必须这 - 是啊
- You have to do it. - Yeah!
我们这是在地狱
- Our life is hell! - Yeah!
如果你们不回去改变
And if you don't go back and change it...
改变
Change it!
是时候终结谎言和妄想了
This ends now. The lies, the delusions.
我受够了他 受够了 他们两个
I'm done with him. I'm done with both of them.
不能打死泰德 爸爸
You're not gonna kill Ted, dad.
他闯进了戴夫格罗尔的家
He broke into Dave grohl's house!
爸爸 慢点
Dad, slow down.
还不知道事情的真相
We don't have the whole story yet.
比尔和泰德 你们逃不过我们
Can't get away from us, bill and Ted.
泰德 他们说得对 他们就是我们
Ted, they're right. They're us.
他们知道我们要做的事
They remember everything we're gonna do!
也就是说
That means we gotta do something
我们得做些他们记不住的事
we can't possibly remember.
开枪吧
Shoot 'em.
不 他们要做那件事
Oh, no. They're gonna do the thing.
不
Oh!
我希望
I was hoping
这次他们不会记得
they wouldn't remember that this time.
禁止出入
No one leaves the building.
怎么办
Dude, what do we do?
不知道才是重点
No idea, that's the point!
我糊涂了
I'm confused!
我也是
Me, too!
泰德可行
Ted, that totally worked!
也许我们最好别知道自己在做什么
Yeah. Maybe we should always not know what we're doing.
什么时间
Time.
还剩47分钟
Forty-seven minutes.
我们还得去更远的未来
All right, we gotta keep going further into the future.
去写了我们歌的未来
At some point, we must've written that song.
- 再多五年 - 好
- Try in five years. - Okay.
老弟
Dude.
那是什么
What's that?
我不知道
I don't know.
绝对不是什么好料
But it's most alarming.
- 比尔 - 我在努力
- Bill? - I'm tryin', dude.
- 比尔 - 快好了
- Bill? - Almost there, dude.
比尔
Billl
搞定了
I got it!
又是你们 我都说了不行
Come on! You again? I said no.
你拒绝我们 你拒绝得了他吗
To us. But I bet you can't say no to this man.
吉米·亨德里克斯先生
Mr. Jimi Hendrix, meet Mr. Louis Armstrong.
这是路易斯·阿姆斯特朗先生
你的那一首曲子真是棒
That lick you played was the cat's meow, man.
这是蓝调 但
It's blues, but also...
怎么说来着 小姐们
What's the word you used, young ladies?
- 迷幻 - 迷幻
- Psychedelic. - Psychedelic.
就是这样
Exactly.
不管你们是谁
Very funny, whoever you are.
路易斯·阿姆斯特朗65岁了
Louis Armstrong's, like, 65 years old.
就说应该请老路易斯来的
Dude, dude, I told you we should've gotten older Louis.
你当时同意的
It was your idea, too!
小姐们在1922年接了我 吉姆
Well, the young ladies picked me up in 1922, Jim.
这证明我们正在组建出色的乐队
Which supports both that we're putting together a most extraordinary band...
我们用的是时间旅行
Yeah. And that we are doing so by traveling all throughout time.
饶了我吧
Come on, give me a break.
他喜欢那首爵士乐
Oh! He dug that jive, eh?
维也纳 1782年
明确的歌名 阿姆斯特朗先生
A definitive one, Mr. Armstrong.
你们喜欢我在未来写的歌是吗
So, what you're all saying is that you love a song that I wrote in my future?
相对是你们的过去
Which is in your past.
但我们在这里
But we're all here in this present.
其实是过去
Which is actually the past?
没错 先生们
Exactly, gentlemen.
真有意思
Fascinating.
是莫扎特先生 没跑了
Herr Mozart. Now we're talkin'.
好啊 小狼狗
Yeah! Hey, Wolfie.
我是吉米
Jimi.
2030年 圣迪马斯监狱
未来派机器人追杀我们
Dude, the future totally sent a killer robot after us.
2030年 圣迪马斯监狱
必须找到这首歌
That's why we gotta find the song, dude.
死亡
Death!
无望的 最后一口气
Hopeless, helpless dying breath. Hopeless, helpless dying breath.
不会是那首歌
This can't possibly be the song, dude.
- 痛苦 - 痛苦
- Pain! - Pain!
- 死亡 - 死亡
- Death! - Death!
欢迎来到末日
Welcome to the end!
不可能
No way!
- 够了 - 够了
- Enough! Stop! - Enough! Stop!
上前来
Come forward.
你们好吗 比尔和泰德
How's it goin', bill and Ted?
喜欢我们的歌吗
How'd you like our song?
- 那是一首歌吗 - 是
Is that a song? Yes!
有点阴暗
It's a little on the dark side,
但很酷
but, you know, that's cool.
你们怎么坐牢了
Why are you guys in prison?
因为五年前的秋天 你们抛下了我们
Oh, maybe because you guys left us to take the fall five years ago. Oh.
对我们就像五分钟之前
That's funny, 'cause for us it's only, like, five minutes ago.
我们现在走了
So, we'll be leaving now.
哪儿也别想去
You're not goin' anywhere, pretty boy.
我们等了好几年想把事情做好
We've been waiting for years to make things right.
但一切都会不同了
But everything's gonna be different.
因为不像上一次的我们 我们真的有一首歌
'Cause unlike those last us's, we actually have a song.
是吗
Is it a song?
是的
Yes!
比尔 泰德 说真的 我们不能带歌回去
Bill, Ted, seriously, we can't take that song back.
你们不会带回去的 卷毛头
Oh, you're not taking it back, curly.
由我们带回去
We're taking it back!
你们就坐牢吧
You're gonna stay here and rot
我们要回去 和老婆重新生活
and we're gonna go get lives and our wives back!
还有团结世界
And unite the world!
拯救现实
And save reality!
- 就你们 - 是的
- You are? - Yes!
不许动 普雷斯顿/罗根
Freeze, preston/logan.
杀了他们什么后果知道吗
You know what happens if he kills them, dude.
那我们也会死
He kills us, dude.
稳住
Hold on!
你要找尔和泰德朋克
You want some bill and Ted, punk?
弄他
Get him!
痛
Pain. Pain, pain.
这不是一首歌
That was not a song.
太可怕了
That was horrible, dude.
有史以来最烂的我们
Those are the worst us's yet, dude!
不过 他们确实救了我们
Yeah. They did save us, though.
是啊
Yeanh.
不
Oh, no!
- 小乔 - 小伊
Ee le === a
- 晦 - 你们好吗
oh, hil - how's it goin'?
- 很好啊 - 天啊是你们吗
- Good. - Oh, my god, is that you?
- 不 不 不 - 我们爱你们
- No, no, no! - We love you guys.
- 得走了 - 该走了
- You've gotta go. - You should probably go.
- 好 - 好
- All right. - Okay.
- 会搞定的 - 我来
- We're gonna fix it! - I got it.
天哪
Oh, good lord. Oh, good heavens.
怎么办
Dude, what now?
故事到最后才有意义
The watch says sometimes things don't make sense till the end of the story.
那怎么办
So?
必须走到最后 泰德
Maybe we gotta go all the way to the end to find out, Ted.
笑到最后 才是胜利者
Most... non-triumphant.
别弱鸡 你是机器人
Pull yourself together. You're a robot!
去下个未来等他们
Get to where they're going next and wait.
时间不多了
We are running out of time.
中国 公元前2600年
玲珑的神话原来是真的 小泰
The myth of ling lun turns out to be true, t.
我知道 而且她是女人
I know. And she's a she.
你系谁呀
加入我们的乐队吗
Hey, you wanna be in our band?
我
是啊
Yeanh.
格罗姆 你一定会喜欢她的
Grom. You're gonna love her.
什么
What?
哈罗 对不起 格罗姆小姐
Hello. Excuse me. Hi. Miss... miss grom...
我也在努力拯救世界 妈妈
Well, I'm trying to save the world, too, mother.
你们这代人没把事做好
It's not like your generation's done that great.
这里情况越来越糟糕了
Oh! It's getting worse and worse here, if you were wondering.
撒哈拉沙漠刚刚在圣迪马斯出现了 妈妈
Ah! Well, the Sahara desert just showed up in San dimas, mother.
伊丽莎白女王正看着它呢
Queen Elizabeth is looking right at it.
不 不 我不会告诉你我在哪的
No. No, I'm not gonna tell you where I am.
万一你派机器人来杀我 妈妈
Because how do I know you won't send your killer robot after me, mom?
我得走了 妈妈
I gotta go, mom.
情况不妙 真的要发生了
This is bad. This is really happening.
会发生什么
What's happening? Whoa ho!
酷仔
Kid cudi!
你好吗
Hey, how's it goin', dude?
谁能告诉我到底怎么了
Can someone please tell me what the hell is happening?
基本上 所有的时空都要完蛋了
Basically all time and space are about to end
除非他们的爸爸在晚上7:17之前 想出一首歌
unless their dads come up with a song by 7:17 P.M.
- 等等 - 什么
Wait. What? Wait. What?
说的不是音乐吗
We thought this was about the music.
是的 但也关于时空
It is. It's also about the end of space and time.
这下糟了
Dude, this is way worse than we thought.
这是全息双场的某种错误吗
So, this is some kind of error in our holographic dual field?
或者是威尔逊循环造成了时间奇点
Or is it a wilsonian loop causing a temporal singularity?
我认为是经典同义因果循环
Well, seems to me your classical tautological causal circuit.
我不知道 我认为是教科书式的纠缠
I don't know. Seems like textbook entanglement to me.
我必须说 你非常理解我们的困境
I must say, your understanding of our dire circumstance is most impressive.
你应该发挥超能力拯救我们的现实
You should put it to good use and help us save reality!
是啊
Yeah!
太好了 这也是时空的终点
That's great. 'Cause it is the end of space and time.
对
Right.
阿姆斯特朗先生 亨德里克斯先生 莫扎特先生
Mr. Armstrong, Mr. Hendrix, herr Mozart,
格罗姆小姐 玲珑小姐 还有库迪先生
miss grom, miss ling lun, and Mr. cudi,
去老爸们的工作室
we're gonna take you into our dads' studio
开始练习
and start practicing.
等老爸们回来后 带着那首能团结世界的歌
So that when our dads get back here with the song that will unite the world,
帮他们演奏
you guys can play it for 'em.
如何
Sound good?
开始练习吧
Let's get practicing.
我靠
Bogus. Oops.
抱歉 大领袖
I'm so sorry, great leader.
不
No.
Oh, no.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
好像没事
I think so, dude.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
也好像没事
I think so, dude.
我们在哪
Dude, where are we?
你们还好吗
Are you guys okay?
我妈妈刚把我杀了
My mother just had me killed.
没想到 她竟然真的杀了我
I didn't think she'd actually do it, but she did.
伟大的音乐家们 很抱歉让你们来到这里
Our sincerest apologies that we're here, great musicians.
我们就想帮助老爸们
We just wanted to help our dads.
但显然我们失败了
Which we clearly utterly failed at.
和平牧草
几点
Time?
加州 圣迪马斯 2067年
老弟
Dude!
小乔和小伊也在吗
Are Jo and Liz here?
在
Yes.
也不在
And no.
什么意思
What did you mean
"在也不在"
"yes and no"?
过去有无限种
There are infinite pasts.
每一种和无限的未来纠缠在一起
Each is entangled with infinite futures.
你说啥呢
So, what are you sayin'?
你们的终点
Where you end up
取决于
all depends
你们的
on what happens
这玩意儿
with this.
那是
Is that...
这是一切的答案
It's the answer to everything.
这就是那首
It's called...
"直面音乐"
"Face the music."
大家
Dudes...
是谁在弹吉他
Who is that on guitar?
是你们俩
It's you two.
是我们
It is us.
直面音乐
Face the music.
普雷斯顿/罗根
Preston/logan!
录制于17点17
Recorded at 7:17 P.M.
在MP46
At mp 46.
这首歌交给你们了
It's in your hands now.
去实现吧
Go make it happen.
谢谢 聪明版的老我们
Thank you, wise old us's.
是的
Yeanh.
我只想说谢谢 比尔
I just wanna say thank you, bill,
谢谢一直帮我
for all the times you've been there for me.
我从来没了解过真正的你 泰德
I feel like I never really knew you, Ted.
是我的错
That's my fault.
我也没对你敞开心扉
I never truly opened myself up to you.
事实是我看到你就像看到我自己
The truth is, I looked at you and saw myself.
我知道 我也有同感
Yeah. I know. Me, too.
对不起 让你失望了 比尔
I'm sorry for the times I let you down, bill.
没有的事 比尔
You never have, bill.
没有的事
You never have.
我不会忘记你 比尔
I'll never forget you, bill.
永远不会
Ever.
回头见 泰德
Catch you later, Ted.
回头见 比尔和泰德
Catch you later, bill and Ted.
他们是好孩子
They're nice boys.
是啊
Yeanh.
我们拿到了真正的歌曲
Dude! We got the actual real song!
现在让全世界听 团结全世界
Now all's we gotta do is figure out how to unite the whole world with it.
并拯救现实
And save reality.
是啊
Yeanh.
- 老弟 - 怎么
Dude! What?
电话亭不见了
The booth is gone.
什么
What?
去哪了
Where did it go?
我不知道 去问刚才的我们吧
I don't know. Let's go back and ask those wise old us's.
希望我们还活着
Yeah. I hope we're still alive.
不许动 普雷斯顿/罗根
Freeze, preston/logan.
最不想看到他
Oh, this is exactly what we don't need right now.
我们不能 我们得回到现在
We can't. We gotta get back to the present, like, now.
如果我们没有那首歌 你会杀了我们
Yeah. Look, we know you were sent here to kill us if we didn't have the song.
但我们有了歌 所以
But we actually do have the song now, so...
等等 你们有那首歌
Wait. You have the song?
错误是犯了
Mistakes were made.
我向你们道歉
Apologies are given.
原谅你了 但我们得走了 机器人老兄
You're forgiven. No problem. But we gotta go, robot dude.
等等 不 必须赎罪
Wait! No, must expiate guilt.
赎什么罪 我们没事
For what? We're fine, dude. Let us go!
为了谋杀家人
For murdering family.
等等 什么
Wait. What?
你说什么
What are you talking about?
我把你们的女儿们都激光了
I lasered your daughters.
你们用激光射了她们
You lasered them?
你激光了我们的女儿
You lasered our daughters?
她们在哪
Where are they?
女儿们
Daughters are
在地狱
in hell.
你把我们的女儿送进了地狱
You sent our daughters to hell?
得去找她们
We have to go get them.
激光我们
Shoot us.
我不能激光你们 你们有歌
I can't shoot you. You have the song.
猜怎么着
Well, guess what?
现在没有歌了
Now there's no song.
别无选择了 机器人
Now you got no choice, robot.
你得杀了我们
You gotta kill us.
不能再杀戮
Can no longer take life.
什么
What?
故障
Failure. Failure. Failure. Failure.
哥们儿
Dude,
必须让他激光我们
we need this guy to laser us but he appears to be having
但他好像神经大条了
some kind of nervous breakdown.
激光吧机器人
Shoot us, robot!
我做不到 出故障了
I can't. I'm a failure.
我根本不配活着
I don't even deserve to live, you know?
激光我们
Shoot us!
我做不到 激光我自己
Can't do it. Shoot myself.
- 等等 不要 - 不能
Wait, don't! You can't!
我们得去救比莉和希雅
We gotta go save Billie and thea.
- 我们去吧 - 好的
Let's do it! Yeah.
抱歉 再见 残酷的世界
I'm so sorry! Goodbye, cruel world!
成功了
It worked!
Yeah!
世界
World!
真没想到
That is unexpected.
是啊 机器人怎么会死呢
Yeah. How can a robot even die?
去找女儿吧
Let's find the girls.
我想一起去
Can I come with you?
好歹他杀了我们
He did kill us.
来吧 机器人
Come on, robot!
等等 我有名字了
Wait. I have a name.
是丹尼斯
It's Dennis.
丹尼斯·麦考伊
Dennis McCoy.
好 走 丹尼斯·麦考伊
Okay. Let's go, Dennis McCoy.
- 希雅 - 比莉
Theal - Billie!
丹尼斯·凯莱布·麦考伊 那是我的全名
Dennis Caleb McCoy. That's the full name.
我们走
Let's go, dude!
感激不尽 对 感激
I feel gratitude. Gratitude.
明白了
Okay, we get it.
你是感激的 没有安全感的
You're a grateful, totally insecure,
一个叫丹尼斯·凯莱布·麦考伊的死机器人
somehow dead robot named Dennis Caleb McCoy.
- 希雅 - 比莉
Theal - Billie!
如何找她们
How're we gonna find them, dude?
我不知道
I don't know, dude.
我也不知道
Yeah, I don't even know, dude.
希雅 比莉
Thea! Billie!
大领袖
Great leader?
比尔和泰德都死了 成功了吗
Bill and Ted are dead. Did it work?
没起作用
No.
什么都没用
Nothing is working.
他们是很好的乐队
They were very nice. Very nice. Good group.
- 乐队 - 是他们往那边走了
- Group? - Yeah. They went that way.
谢谢 恶魔
Thanks, demons.
- 没问题 - 享受地狱吧 你们
- You betcha. - Enjoy hell, y'all.
- 谢谢 恶魔们 - 玩得开心点
- Thanks, demons. - Have a good time, boys.
不对劲
I know that's strange.
什么鬼 机器人
What is that, a robot?
那是地狱机器人
Yeah, that's a robot in hell.
- 希雅 - 比莉
- Thea? - Billie?
- Thea? - Billiel
不
nol
- 不接受道歉 妈妈 - 凯莉
- apology not accepted, mother. - Kelly?
比尔和泰德来了 你那边成功了吗 妈妈
Bill and Ted are here. Did it work, mom?
果然没错
Yeah. That's what I thought.
她们在哪
Where are they?
那边
They're that way.
我是丹尼斯·凯莱布·麦考伊
I'm Dennis Caleb McCoy. I am so...
不
No! No.
比圣诞节那次还要严重
Oh, yeah. This is way worse than the Christmas incident.
你们给他取名丹尼斯 我前男友也叫这名字
And you named him Dennis? After my ex?
滚出去
Get outta here!
- 希雅 比莉 - 比莉 希雅
- Theal! Billie! - Billie! Thea!
老爸们
Dads!
你们好吗
How're you doin'?
但我们死了
Well, you know, we're dead.
我们在地狱里
And we're in hell.
但你们好吗
But how're you doin'?
我们很好
We're good!
看看我们找到了谁
Yeah. Look who we found.
爸爸
Dad?
晦 泰德
Hi, Ted.
我错了 我是说 你们在地狱
I was wrong. I mean, you're here.
这意味着你们也穿越了时空
Which implies that you also traveled through time
而你们的老婆居然是公主
and that your wives actually are princesses.
这证明了 你们必须写出
All of which proves that it is imperative
那首能团结全世界的歌
that you write the song that will unite the entire world.
并拯救现实
And save reality.
等等 还有附带条件的吗
Wait, is that new?
对啊
Yeah.
那么 我该帮助你们 而不是批评你们
Well, then, I should help you instead of criticizing you.
我非常 非常 非常抱歉
And I am very, very, very sorry.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, dad!
谢谢 罗根警长
Yeah, thanks, chief Logan!
我不是在跟你说话 比尔
I wasn't talking to you, bill.
好
Oh. Cool.
老爸们 这是我们为你们组建的乐队
Well, dads, this is the band we put together for you.
这是吉米·亨德里克斯 路易斯·阿姆斯特朗
This is Jimi Hendrix, Louis Armstrong...
还有莫扎特 玲珑 还有格罗姆
And Mozart, and ling lun, and grom.
幸会 先生们
A pleasure, gentlemen.
你们养育了两个好女儿
You raised two fine young girls.
现在算是吧
- Kinda am now, I think. - Yeah.
很荣幸见到你们所有人
It's a great honor to meet you all.
欢迎来到 地狱 抱歉
Yeah. Welcome to, and sorry about, hell.
我的错
My bad.
那是丹尼斯·凯莱布·麦考伊
Well, that's Dennis Caleb McCoy.
我们见过
We've met.
他杀了我们
He killed us.
很抱歉我激光了你们
I'm really sorry that I lasered you all.
还有
And
我只想告诉你们
I just need to tell you...
我叫丹尼斯·凯莱布·麦考伊
My name is Dennis Caleb McCoy, and...
谢谢 丹尼斯
Thank you, Dennis.
谢谢来找我们
Well, thanks for coming to get us.
我们怎么离开
How're we gonna get outta here?
去找死神谈谈
We're gonna go talk to death.
他不是还在生你们的气吗
Well, isn't he still mad at you guys?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
- 我们也还在生他的气 - 是啊
- And we're still mad at him. - Yeah.
还剩19分钟
Nineteen minutes.
大家 跟着我们
Everyone, follow us.
很好
Yes way!
满分81分 我有75分
Best 75 out of 81.
- 他一个人玩跳房子吗 - 我又赢了
- Is he playing hopscotch by himself? - I have bested you again.
他很可怜的样子
He looks miserable, dude.
厉害
Yes!
他在作弊
Dude, he's cheating!
厉害
Yes!
- 走吧 - 我们走
- Take a hike. - Let's go, dude.
祝好运老爸们
Good luck, dads.
- 乖一点 - 好的
- Be sweet. - Okay.
好的
Okay.
你好 死神
Hey, death.
啊哈 这不是威史组合吗
Why, if it isn't the wyld stallyns.
你们又想告我
Have you come to sue me again?
没有 死神 完全不是嘱
No, death. Not at all.
死神我们只想和你谈谈
No. We just need to talk to you, death.
跟这只手谈吧
Talk to the hand.
一秒钟就好
It will only take a second, dude.
- 死神 - 拜托 大哥
- Death! - Come on, dude.
是谁
Who is it?
比尔和泰德
Bill and Ted.
怎么了 你们的限制令失效了吗
What? Did your restraining order run out?
法官改变主意了吗
Did the judge change his mind?
所以 现在我可以接近你们了
So, now I am allowed to get close to you?
是不是太近了
Hmm? Is this too close?
死神
Death.
我们不想起诉你
We didn't want to sue you, dude.
- 记住 客气点 - 说得对
- Remember, be sweet, dude. - You're right.
你想占用威史组合这名字
You tried to take the name wyld stallyns.
我就是威史组合
I was wyld stallyns.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你们把我踢出来 是因为你们嫉妒我
You kicked me out because you was jealous of me.
- 不不不 大哥 - 是是是
- No, no, no, dude. - Yes, yes, yes.
你退出乐队是为了自立门户
You quit the band to go out on your own!
你们不让我演奏
You wouldn't let me play!
那是 因为你独奏了40分钟的贝斯
Dude, you were playing 40-minute bass solos.
除了你 别人都没得演
No one but you could play!
我弹得很好呢
I was in the groove!
什么啊
What?
说的是40分钟的独奏
Those 40-minute solos,
是演出的亮点
that was the highlight of your shows.
这也难怪你们会落魄
It's no wonder you went down in the tubes.
该怎么办
What're we gonna do?
死亡 今天我们拜访的原因是
Death, the reason we came here is 'cause
我们必须去某个MP46的地方演奏 就现在
we have to play a song at some place called mp 46, like, right now.
否则时间会崩溃
All of time is gonna fold in on itself, dude.
我被降职了
I have been demoted down here
因为我带着两个
because I took two
所谓的"朋友"回到阳间 他们不该复活的
so-called "friends" back up who should not have gone back up.
既然你们来这里
So, if that is why you're here...
抱歉 我不欠你们抱歉
Sorry, not sorry.
再见
Bye!
- 现在怎么办 - 我不知道
- What now? - I don't know, dude.
老爸们 我们有个想法
Dads, we have an idea.
可以试试吗
You mind if we try?
这家伙是有史以来最好的低音贝斯手
I mean, the dude is the most rad bass player, like, ever.
是的
Yeanh.
那就试试
Please.
- 试试就试试 - 来
- Okay. - Come on.
- 好 - 他是混蛋
- All right. - He's kind of a dick.
好
Okay.
老爸们 你们该在外面等
Dads, we think you should wait outside.
打扰 死神先生阁下
Excuse us, Mr. death, sir.
很高兴又见到您 死神先生阁下
It's good to see you again, Mr. death, sir.
这不是小比尔和小泰德吗
Well, if it isn't little bill and little Ted.
我们仍是你最忠实的粉丝
We're still your hugest fans.
是的
Yeanh.
嘱
Oh.
不要奉承我
Don't fudge with me.
哪有 阁下
We're not fudging with you, sir.
- 这是合法的 - 是啊
It's legit. Yeah.
- 真的吗 - 是啊
Really? Yeah.
我是说"孤独的灵魂冲浪者"
I mean, the lonely soul surfer
是1998年最被低估的专辑
was the most underrated album in 1998.
乐评人不喜欢它
The critics hated it.
问题他们不能欣赏一整张的贝斯专辑
Well, they just weren't ready for an album that was all bass.
他们说"太普通了"
"It was all over the place," they said.
他们说"乱到一塌糊涂"
"It was a raging, confused mess," they said.
他们说"甚至比’苍白的苍白’更糟糕"
"It was even worse than pale on pale," they said.
这个嘛
Well...
一部分是这样
It was, in parts.
但其他部分
But in other parts...
"我永远不会被爱"的序曲 是最棒的
The outro in "I'll never be loved" is the most bodacious.
我是指在"苍白不哭"的副歌前的最后三小节
I mean, the last three bars before the chorus in "too pale to cry..."
那好
Oh, well...
你们觉得"和迪博士一起跳舞"里的副歌怎样
What did you think of the hook in "boogie down with doctor d?"
还能怎么说
What can we even say?
疯了 独一无二的左手技巧
Insane. We've never seen left-hand technique like that.
我知道 那是我自创的
I know! I was self-taught.
你这技能棒到呆
You have some crazy, crazy skills, dude!
这个嘛
Well...
- 你还缺少一样 - 什么
- You know what you need? - Hmm?
你还缺一个乐队
You just need a band.
而乐队需要你
And the band needs you.
- 小泰 - 小比
Oh.
快进来
Come on in.
老爸们 你们有话想对死神说吗
Dads, is there something you would like to say to death?
抱歉我们之间的纠纷 死神
We're sorry for how things went between us, death.
是啊
Yeanh.
真诚的抱歉
Sincerely sorry.
抱歉 我被名利冲昏了头脑
I am sorry that fame went to my head.
很容易让人上瘾
It's very intoxicating.
很喜欢有你一起演奏
We really did love playing with you, dude.
我们确实很厉害吧
We really did rock, didn't we?
那是当然的
We definitely did.
如果还来得及死神
And if it's not too late, death...
你愿不愿意重新加入
Would you consider rejoining...
威史组合
Wyld stallyns?
我
Oh, I...
我觉得可以
I suppose.
好了 走
Okay, let's go!
太好了
Right. Right.
我是丹尼斯你们好
It's Dennis. Hi.
- 我迷路了 - 上车丹尼斯
- I got lost. - Get in, Dennis.
- 好的 - 谢谢
Okay. Thank you, guys.
你好 酷仔
Hey, kid cudi.
- 你们好 大家好 - 嗷
- Oh, hello. Hello, everyone. - Ow!
好了 朋友们
Hey. Hey. Yeah, okay, friends.
该摇滚了
Let's rock!
你说"该摇滚了"时 真酷啊
It was cool when you said, "let's rock"
因为它让我想摇滚
because it made me want to rock. Uh-huh.
不能只摇滚
You don't just get to rock.
要赢得摇滚
You got to earn the right to rock.
还剩11分钟
Dude! We got 11 minutes.
谁知道MP46在哪里
Anyone know where mp 46 is?
得看你怎么看
Depends on your perspective.
如果要去量子领域
To really dig the groove of the quantum realm,
必须选择合适的入口
you gotta choose a place to dig it from.
明白吗
Dig?
有人知道MP46在哪吗
Anyone know where mp 46 is?
赶不上飞机了
We're never gonna make our flight.
哼
Hmm.
迪克 迪克 看
Deac, deac. Look at that. Whoa!
交给我
I got this.
停
Stop!
我们回来了
We're back!
什么
What?
这下糟了
This is bad.
超级糟
Really bad.
大家走
Okay, guys, let's go!
速度
Come on!
速度 莫扎特
Come on, Mozart.
泰德 即使我们知道演出地点
Oh, Ted! Even if we knew
比尔 看
Bill, look!
这是MP46 没道理啊
This is mp 467? It makes no sense.
为什么要在这里演奏
How can the song happen right here?
因为就是这里
Because this is where it happened.
泰德 你说的太对了
Ted, you're right, dude!
但我们拿什么来演奏
But, dude, what're we gonna play?
我不知道
I don't know, dude.
比尔和泰德 这是我留着的
Bill and Ted? I saved these.
不知是否有用 但是
I'm not sure if they're of any use, but...
- 谢谢 丹尼斯 - 老爸们
- Thanks, Dennis. - Dads!
老爸们 MP46
Dads! Mp 46.
万事俱备
And the band is ready to play.
只欠这首歌
Alls we need is the song.
希雅
Thea.
比莉
Billie.
也不知道该怎么说
We don't know how to tell you this.
我们没歌
We don't have the song.
等等
Wait.
你们没有
You don't?
对
No.
抱歉
We're sorry.
该说抱歉的是我们 老爸们
We're sorry, dads.
我们真的很想帮你们
Yeah, we really wanted to help you out with this.
我没看错吧
Dude, you seeing what I'm seeing?
普雷斯顿
Preston?
罗根
Logan?
普雷斯顿/罗根
Preston/logan.
哇
Whoa!
怎么回事 老爸们
What is it, dads?
是你们
It's you!
什么啊
What?
一直都是你们 但被我们忽略了
It was you the whole time. We just didn't see it.
我们又不会写歌
We can't write music.
我们只会听歌
Whatever... we just listen to stuff.
用喜欢的东西
From things we like.
拼凑一下
And we just kind of put stuff together.
也许你们听的不多
Yeah, maybe you just listen a little,
做事凭兴趣
make things you like.
然后随便拼凑
And put it all together.
女儿们 你们不是我们的后援
Girls, you're not here to back us.
我们才是你们的后援
We're here to back you.
我们是你们的乐队
We're your band.
哇
Whoa!
跟着我们
Follow us!
拿乐器
Here you go. Instruments!
哇
Whoa!
老弟 我想到一件事
Dude, I just thought of something.
什么事 泰德
What is it, Ted?
如果光凭一首歌
How is just listening to a song...
就能团结全世界
Gonna unite the whole world...
从古至今吗
Throughout all of time?
问得好 老哥
That is a good question, dude.
所有人都要听到这首歌
It's almost like they'd all have to hear it in order to play it.
泰德 这样才能团结全世界
Ted, of course! That's how we're gonna unite 'em.
必须让所有人参与
We get 'em to play along.
既然如此 我们要让所有人参与
Well, if that's true, alls we gotta do is get to everyone throughout all time.
把乐器拿给他们
Yeah, and get 'em instruments, dude.
还剩7分25秒
In 7 minutes and 25 seconds.
手鼓怎样
What about a tambourine?
用它来摇滚能有多难
I mean, how hard can it be to rock with that?
手鼓并不简单
Tambourine is not as easy as it looks.
那跳舞呢 我跳舞很不错的
What about dancing? I'm a very gifted dancer.
你会跳舞吗
You dance?
真的吗
Really?
要不你过去那边排练跳舞
Why don't you go over there and rehearse your dance?
好啊
Okay.
这边没电
Dude, we have no power!
不用说 交给我
Say no more. On it.
好
Okay.
好了 小乔
There! Oh, Jo.
- 希雅多 - 威廉姆
Theodore. “William!
- 乔安娜 - 小伊
Joannal “Liz!
晦
Hi
我们四人幸福生活在一起的现实 你们找到了吗
Did you find a reality where we're all happy together?
找到了
We did.
在现在这个现实中 我们是最幸福的
We realized we're happiest in this reality.
这才像话
Sweet!
我们刚才是不是听到
Now, did we hear you say something about
你们说要分发乐器
distributing instruments all throughout time?
准备 小泰
Ready, t7
五 六 五 六 七 八
five, six, five, six, seven, eight!
我的天 什么声音
Oh, my god, what's happening?
对不起 库迪先生
Excuse me, Mr. cudi, sir?
我们的老婆刚刚穿越了多个现实世界
Our wives just traveled through multiple realities.
后来她们意识到
And in doing so, they realized...
- 是同时发生的 - 同时
They're all happening - simultaneously. - Simultaneously.
我们要把乐器拿到无限多的地方去吗
Do we need individual us's to take instruments to infinite places?
好
Okay.
实际上有相反的观点
See, contrary to what some have argued,
普遍波函数
universal wave function is,
从认识论上讲
epistemologically speaking,
既循环又分离换句话说
both cyclic and separating. In other words...
对不起 酷仔 我不想打断你
Excuse me, kid cudi. I don't mean to be rude,
但我们还剩4分半钟
but we have, like, four and a half minutes.
大领袖 我们得走了 这里不安全
Madam. Madam! We have to go. It's not safe to be in here.
还能去哪
Where were you thinking of going?
是月食
I think it's a lunar eclipse.
那不是月食
That is not lunar, you guys.
这是灾难 小泰
This is a disaster, t.
怎么办 小比
What are we gonna do, b?
停
Stop!
你们得进入多重现实的量子叠加状态
All you need to do is go in the quantum superposition with multiple realities.
如何做
But how?
电话亭显然是通往量子领域的隧道
Dudes, the booth is obviously a tunnel to the quantum realm.
快去吧
Go, go, go!
- 谢谢 库迪先生 - 谢谢 库迪先生
- Thank you, Mr. cudi! - Thank you, Mr. cudi!
站
Station. Station!
- 格罗姆 - 格罗姆 你先开始
- Grom! - Grom, you start!
- 不 - 停
- No, no, no... - Stop, stop!
看
Look.
现在死神上
And now, death!
最好来一点
Well... it's... maybe something like...
"苍白不哭"
"Too pale to cry."
- 最后那段 - 最神奇的那段
- That last riff? - Amazing! Yeah.
让所有人演奏什么
What're we gonna tell people to play?
- 我们马上回来 - 好的
- We'll be right back. - Okay.
读一下无限数字
Read me the number for the infinite, dude.
6-9... 6-9
2-9-9
- 协奏曲怎样 - 好 去告诉他
- how about that concerto? - Okay, go tell him.
莫扎特
Mozart.
3-4-5.5
5-1-0-1
我和姑娘们道别了
I already said goodbye to the girls.
但我想留下跳舞
But I wanna stay here and dance.
丹尼斯
Dennis.
祝好运 朋友们
Good luck, my excellent friends.
谢谢 凯莉
Thanks, Kelly.
再见 丹尼斯
Later, Dennis.
我叫丹尼斯 丹尼斯·麦考伊
My name is Dennis. Dennis McCoy.
2-7-1-8.
再快点 小迪
Faster, you know? Yeah! Now, d.
好的
Oh, yeah. Yeah!
看这
Watch this!
吉米 为了胜利
Jimi, for the win!
1-8-2-8-3-5
好的 姑娘们说C大调
okay. Okay. The girls said c major.
每分钟113次
113 beats per minute.
- 明白了 - 好
- Got it. - All right. Yeah.
455 51
4-5-55.1
- 435 - 也许按无限按钮就好
- 4-3-95... - Guys, maybe just press the infinite button.
也对
Oh, yeah.
好的
Yeanh.
最后一件事
One last thing.
我爱你 伊丽莎白
I love you, Elizabeth.
我也爱你 乔安娜
I love you, Joanna.
我们知道
We know.
我也爱你
I love you.
- 好了 走 - 好的
- Okay, let's go. - Okay.
你好 迪克
How's it goin', deac?
蜜西
Missy.
告诉你们 我是无限的
In case you're wondering, I'm essentially an infinite me.
回头见
Catch you later.
棒呆了
Outstanding! Yeah!
- 厉害 - 厉害
- Excellent! - Excellent!
老爸们
Dads!
等等
Wait.
圣迪马斯 噪起来
San dimas, make some noise! Yeah!
十 九 八 七
Ten, nine...
八 七
Eight, seven...
六
Six...
- 五 - 老爸们
- Five... - Dads!
四 三
Four, three...
一
Two, one.
大领袖 你来看
Madam, you need to see this.
你父亲会为你骄傲的
Your father would be so proud of you.
- 再见 - 再见 酷仔
- Bye! - Bye, kid cudi! - Bye! - See ya, kid cudi!
成功了
It's working!
耶
Yeah!
这首歌带来的改变
And so, it wasn't so much
并没有那么多
the song that made the difference.
重要的是大家都有参与
It was everyone playing it together.
所以才会团结全世界
And it worked.
老哥
Dude,
你咽气了吗
are you dead yet?
没有
No.
你翘了吗
Are you?
没翘
No.
在我们归西之前 还有一件事
There's one more thing we need to do before we go.
那是当然
Definitely.
准备 比尔
Ready, bill?
好了 泰德
Ready, Ted.
一 - 二
One... two...
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four!
好
Okay.
Yeah. Okay.
- 好 - 好
- Okay. - Okay.
宝刀不老
We still
豪气犹存
got it.
- 比尔 - 怎么了
Hey, bill. Yeah?
我得坐下
Okay, I have to sit down.
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 刚才很好玩 - 超级棒
- That was fun. - That was good.
护士妹
Nurse!